Silver Fox Foxy, the Merciless Interference.
This race is really heating up.
The next course obstacle, the long coral reef is dead ahead.
Leading the race is Portia and the Cutie Wagon.
Pursuing close behind are the Straw Hats and the Barrel Tiger and Adleas and Cloaks.
Whoa, they're like Chopper's antlers.
Why is the coral in this reef so long?
Why is it sticking out like that?
Whatever, let's just get through it.
Look, that weird reef is causing some unusual currents to form.
Going in blind's not a good idea.
Ugh, I can't believe this stupid race has lasted this long.
We're counting on you, Monda.
And don't forget, there's someone on land looking for every opportunity to sabotage this race.
Our boss, Silver Fox Foxy.
Just what does he have in store for us?
Yeah, get him, boss.
It's only a matter of time.
Wait, wait, what's this?
The Straw Hats are slowing down.
Come on, Nami, keep rowing.
Not yet.
Not yet?
They're getting further ahead of us.
I know, okay?
We're not going in yet.
Sanji, you wait here too.
Anything you say, Nami.
The Cutie Wagon takes advantage of this opportunity and plunges forward into the long coral reef.
Let's go, Monda.
Hey, wait a minute.
What's happening?
Monda!
Huh, they came back.
What?
The Cutie Wagon has been pushed back out of the reef.
What's happening down there?
I don't understand.
See, I knew there was something weird about those currents.
Now, let's get moving, Usopp.
Right.
You too, Sanji.
Pick up the pace and follow me.
Aye, aye.
Let's try this again, Monda.
Come on, this way.
What's this?
The Straw Hats are picking up speed.
All three boats are about to enter the long coral reef at the same time.
Huh.
The barrel tiger and at least it floats haven't been pushed back.
Hey, what's that?
Ha-ha!
And there you have it.
The devilish interference we've all been waiting for.
He's some kind of smokescreen.
You gotta be kidding.
What's that idiot up to?
Hey, I can't see where we're going.
Ah!
Now the reef will be far too dangerous for the Straw Hat teams to proceed any further.
And there you have it.
Operation Whiteout successful.
Let's see how you navigate through this reef when you can't even see through it.
You sure it worked?
What the hell?
They made it through with no trouble at all!
How is that possible?
I called it.
Incredible!
The Straw Hat sailed through the long coral reef with ease!
But what about the cutie wagon?
Oh no!
It seems they've been pushed back again!
Hey, the boat is moving on its own.
What's going on here, Nami?
This place is a maze of currents.
Currents?
Right!
That giant whirlpool ahead of us is causing smaller whirlpools to form within the reef, resulting
in these strange currents.
Doesn't matter if we can't see, their course won't change.
As long as we take the right entrance, these currents will guide the boat along all by themselves.
Incredible!
You're a miracle!
That's what you can do when you've got the best navigator on the Grand Line and your crew!
Take that!
Nami Swan!
You're amazing!
Damn it!
But they won't be celebrating for long!
Once they're out of the reef, they head straight into the long ring!
Long coral reef, long ring, it's just one long thing after a...
No, Zob!
Stop freaking out and use it!
Use what?
The impact dial!
But I don't have it with me, though!
No, no, no!
Yeah, then what's this?
What's that?
We're dead!
How did you...
Come on, hurry!
If you don't use it soon, we'll be sucked down into the giant whirlpool!
Why are you smiling?
You know what it's like to use that thing?
If I do it again, I'll break my shoulder!
That's a risk I'm totally willing to take!
That's because it's my shoulder!
Impact dial!
Hey!
Come on, we're running out of time here!
So that's why you've been acting so calm, huh?
You had this plan from the very beginning, didn't you?
Well, it's been a nice life!
Treinta flu!
Now, do it, Long Nose!
Do it, my butt!
Fine, then!
Oh!
The barrel tiger and at least it floats have picked up some tremendous speed!
No, wait!
They're not just going faster!
They're flying!
They're leaping right over Long Cape!
They have now taken the lead!
But wait!
Oh, crap!
This isn't good!
Ah!
Whoops, it broke.
At least it floats as Crash landed on Long Cape and broken into pieces!
It can no longer continue the race!
Such a shame!
At least it floats is now disqualified!
I'm so sorry, Nami, my dear!
Don't worry about us!
Just continue the race!
Okay, we will!
And with that move, the barrel tiger now has a commanding lead!
Does this mean defeat for the indomitable cutie wagon?
We were way too easy on them!
Okay, Portia, hang on tight!
I'm counting on you!
Time to fish engine!
They're not out of the race yet!
By fusing fish man muscle with the fin of a shark, the cutie wagon has doubled its engine speed!
They're blazing through the coral and closing the gap!
The race is now half over!
Meanwhile, the barrel tiger desperately paddles on!
Usopp!
Wake up!
Where am I?
Get up and start paddling!
Your arm seems to be bending the wrong way.
What is that?
Looks like a course marker.
Turn right.
Ah, guess we'll turn right then.
What the hell we will!
What's this?
She broke it!
Our boss is blowing number 18!
Operation Life of M has failed!
What a formidable woman!
Does she not believe in anything in this world?
He can't it, jackass!
She's foul mouthed too!
The race continues with the barrel tiger maintaining its strong lead!
What are these columns of water?
They are now clearing the long waves that reach high into the sky!
Was that supposed to be natural?
Oh, Grandma.
Oh, boss.
I mean, oh, Grandma.
Maybe my time on this earth is over.
The boss unleashes his third nasty trick.
Hey, you!
A dying granny over here!
Won't you stop and help me?
Unbelievable!
She completely ignores a child and his sick, helpless grandmother!
The only thing she cares about is getting what she wants!
How cold-hearted!
The Ice Queen Navigator Nami!
I told you to can it!
I'd never fall for a ridiculous trick like that!
Did I mention she was foul-mouthed?
Huh?
Hey, look!
It's the finish line!
This race will soon be decided!
Not so fast!
Not gonna be that easy!
The cutie wagon is closing in quickly!
These are the final moments of Round 1's donut race!
Who will win?
I told you!
These lame tricks won't work!
She even sees through Operation Fake Goal!
Formidable! Truly formidable!
And now I have a question for her!
What is it like to go through life so dated?
Piss off!
It's too late for her! Her heart is cold! She has no soul!
But the real goal is nearby. We're getting close.
I'm not using that dial again!
Yeah, yeah, I know!
Meanwhile, Porcha and the Cutie Wagon have tragically stopped at the fake goal!
What's going on? Who won the race?
What the? Where did everybody go?
The purity of your heart is astounding! Pay attention, Porcha! You've been tricked!
Those guys are complete idiots! I'd die of embarrassment if we lost to them!
They'd take one of our crew, too! That's worse!
Oh no! This goal is a complete fake!
What? Who would do something so evil?
The barrel tiger is finally approaching the long bamboo cape!
The goal is just beyond it! They're in the homestretch!
Hey, he's right! I can see the finish line!
Wait up!
But they're catching up to us!
There's no way we'll beat them at this speed!
I've got an idea! Usopp, can you shoot down that bamboo?
Bamboo? Alright!
Like that?
Yes! More! More!
Moja! Capote! Move it! Full speed ahead!
We'll ram them and sink that stupid boat to the bottom of the ocean!
Take that! And that! And that! And that! And that! And that! And that! That! That!
Whoa! Bingo!
Oh no! Capote, you say something!
I've had it! They're gonna pay for this!
Cutie! Baton!
What's that? Some kind of magic flower trick?
Flower!
Chicken!
Oh, flower shoulda get... Hey! Look out!
Look out!
Oh no! Looks like we've sprung a leak!
Don't worry! We can make it! We're almost to the goal!
Keep paddling!
Round one of the Davy Back Fight the Donut Race is about to come to a close!
Oh! Gorgeous!
Come on!
Stay strong, Munda! We can't let him beat us!
We're going to lose if we don't do something! Bring us up alongside him!
Right, boss!
I can't see! I wonder who's winning!
Made it just in time!
Alright! Nami's team is winning!
Robin, baby! Nami, my darling! You look so hot when you're going fast!
Man, you guys almost won!
What do you mean? We're totally gonna win!
Not so fast! Take a look over there! Our boss is coming!
Yeah? So what? What can he do?
Our boss is just like you! He has devil fruit powers!
He he he he he!
He he he!
Slow, slow beam!
And the winner is the Cutie Wagon!
The hero of the first round of the Davy Back Fight is our very own idol, Porcha!
Way to go!
Thank you! Thanks everyone!
You're the greatest, Porcha!
It's only natural, I won!
Looks like we're about to get a new crew member!
There's nobody that can beat the Foxy Pirates! We always win!
Now it's time for you guys to play up! We're taking one of your crew!
You guys hurt? Is everybody okay? Robin?
Yes. We're alright.
What the heck happened out there?
I'd like to know the same thing!
We'd all like to know what happened! Did we really lose somehow?
You looked like you were gonna win, but then you suddenly slowed down and they passed you!
There's nothing strange about that! It was caused by slow-mo photon!
Hey, what did you do to Nami's team, you smug bastard?
What's a slow-mo photon?
They are particles unlike any others known to modern science!
Whatever this light touches, be it an animal, a liquid, a solid, or even a gas,
will lose a fixed amount of its velocity, while simultaneously retaining all its other energy!
You're dumb! That makes no sense at all!
He just mocked me!
Oh! So are you okay? No way! Something that ridiculous is just...
Impossible? Is that what you're thinking?
Surely you know that such a naive, childish claim has no merit out here on these waters!
Everything they touch slows down, that's the power of slow-mo photons!
Now that makes sense! Why didn't you say so before?
After I ate the slow, slow fruit, I became a slow-motion man, capable of producing these particles from my body!
Observe!
A floating cannonball!
The slow, slow beam!
The effect lasts approximately 30 seconds, after which the object will regain its original speed as if nothing had ever happened!
Can't believe your eyes I take it, this...
Oh no!
I get it! So that's why we didn't win the race!
It also explains why they're so overly confident about these games!
What a joke of a devil fruit power!
It doesn't matter! You guys lost! You know all the rules and you agree to all the terms!
The donut race is over! And we are the winners!
Aw, too bad for you guys!
That concludes round one! And now we shall commence with the awarding of the prize!
The winning captain will select a member of the opposing crew!
My first selection is none other than...
You! The Doctor! Tony Tony Chopper!
Bring him to me at once!
No! No! Stop it!
Oh no! Chopper!
Such a rare creature! You're even softer than I imagined you'd be!
Oh, boss me! I hold him too!
You're so damn cute! And he's ours now!
Chopper!
So that creep had his eyes set on Chopper, huh?
Well, I suppose that he is among the rarest of rare animals.
Or maybe he collects cute things?
You know, I wouldn't rule out a fur fetish.
Why does it even matter? Focus, people! That freak over there just took our friend!
You guys!
Alright, Doctor Chopper. Enough of all that. You're one of my crew now.
You need to pledge your loyalty to me. And you can start by putting on this mask.
You guys!
I'm so sorry that we lost Chopper! We did our best!
Farewell!
He is truly a rarity!
Our Mario Talking Reindeer! He's so amazing!
We're gonna get along great! Here!
Welcome aboard!
You guys!
Listen!
I only went out to sea because of you!
I won't!
No! I refuse!
Luffy! You invited me!
I sent sail to be one of the Straw Hats!
I won't go with them!
Please!
No!
I am the ship's doctor of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Tony Tony Chopper!
I won't go!
Quit your belly aching, Chopper!
It's disgraceful!
Uh... Zoro?
You made the choice to set sail as a pirate.
Only you!
And now you have to live with the consequences of that decision.
We agreed to the terms of this game.
You, Usopp, and everyone else did the best they could.
Not one pirate worth his salt is gonna sympathize with those tears.
A man would suck it up and quietly watch the rest of this game.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you know how he must be feeling?
Boil me or cook me alive!
Give me your worst, you bastards!
Chopper?
Atta boy.
Whoa! That swordsman is totally awesome!
All right! You teach him a lesson, Zoro!
Yeah! Get Chopper back!
Hey, boss! Let's take him next!
That reindeer's not guns!
Let's get the second event started.
So inspirational, I can't stop crying!
Yeah, we still have two rounds left of this.
There's no way we're letting these jerks take our emergency food supply.
Sachi!
We're counting on you!
The exchange is complete and the excitement explodes as the daily backbite enters round two!
Hey, wasn't Chopper supposed to be in the second round? How can he compete if they took him?
Good point.
That's one of the most thrilling parts of the game!
Remember the rules, you cannot change your team's roster.
No replacements allowed!
In other words, only the remaining two contestants can participate in round two's game!
The groggy ring! This gives the foxy team an artly advantage!
What? That's not fair!
Actually, you could sit this one out, too.
Nah, but feel free to do the same thing, you loser.
It's hard to believe that they're gonna work together as a team.
What was that?
Knock it off!
And the rules of the groggy ring!
We have a playing field, and we have two goals!
Knock the ball into the goal, and you win!
However, the ball isn't actually a ball!
The balls are people!
Both teams must select someone to be the ball!
Make your selection!
You heard him! Which one of you two guys is gonna be the ball?
Ball marker!
Who said you get to pick? You're the ball, you moss-headed bastard!
Oh, there it is! Their entrance theme song!
It's time to welcome back the undisputed elites of the groggy ring!
They are undefeated! Unbeatable!
Unstammable!
Yeah! Crush'em!
Push-up! The famous groggy monsters have taken the field!
Behold, the kings of the ring!
First up is Full Dash Hamburg!
Following behind is Taco Machine Pickles!
And last but not least, the half-giant, half-fish-man himself!
Big Pan Luatang!
This is literally a monstrous march!
Yeah! Yeah!
What is that?
That fish-man is ginormous!
Oh crap! He's the one wearing the ball marker!
Fish-fish!
You'll never beat him!
Disappointed?
Not at all.
!
On the next one piece round to shoot it into the groggy ring